MIRCEA NUTA

mircea.nuta@gmail.com | 07494690676 | Malborough Avenue 26, Edgware, Middlsex HA8 8UH

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

IT Manager with 3rd line support experience and team lead background with more then 10 years experience in both private or public cloud infrastructures (AWS certified Sysops and Solution Architect - Associated). Broad industry experience includes healthcare, automotive and digital marketing. Familiar with user support, Windows Server, DHCP, DNS, Active Directory, ADSync, Microsoft Exchange, Office 365, Firewalls, Networking, SAN's, thin clients, server and desktop virtualization using VMware and Citrix (XenApp and XenDesktop), Sitecore architecture, Atlassian suite, CI/CD tools.

SKILLS

- AWS (VPC, Route53, EC2, Cloudwatch, S3, IAM, Cloudformation, System Manager, Cloudfront ...)
- Windows Server DNS; DHCP; Active Directory
- Server and desktop virtualization (Citrix, VMware)
- Exchange and Office 365
- Sitecore
- Networking
- Storage: Netapp
- Firewalls : Sophos; Fortinet

- Self-motivated
- Process implementation
- Project management
- Time management
- Good communicator
- Strategic thinking

WORK HISTORY

Jan 2018 – Present **Site Reliability Engineer** Usource Technology - Clujnapoca, Cluj

As a site reliability engineer I'm providing support for our clients in US on deploying and maintenance of the aws environments supporting CMS applications. The team has 6 members (4 operations, 2 engineers) and together we have the mission to assure continuous operation, support for the content management systems like AEM, Hybris, Sitecore and fulfill our SLA agreements. We use various tools for deployment, monitoring, security checks, incident and change management like Jira, Prtg, Sumologic, CloudWatch, NewRelic, ServiceNow, Nessus Scan, Git, Stash, Bamboo, Office 365. I'm designing and implementing aws infrastructures, automating with cloudformation, system

Apr 2005 - Dec 2017

IT Manager

Eckerle Automotive Romania - Cluj-Napoca, Cluj

manager, database migration to AWS RDS, monitoring and providing 3rd level support on application and os level (windows, centos) issues.

Eckerle Automotive part of Eckerle Group is producing subansambles for automotive industry specially for Bosch in multiple locations around the world. Initially hired for implementing the company ERP then promoted as IT manager.

Responsabilities

In charge for all IT and communication infrastructure i had to assure an optimal functionality for all IT systems (pc's, phones, thin clients, printers, servers, communication system, dell servers, netapp storage, cisco switches, cisco wifi, Sophos firewall, surveillance system). Responsible for backup strategy, disaster recovery procedure, security, vpn connections, user support (windows environment), enterprise antivirus, designing and implementing new ERP processes, data security., I implemented different projects on the group level like line counter application, OTRS ticketing system, desktop virtualization using citrix xenapp, xendesktop and thin clients, desktop migration to a remote datacenter in DE and server virtualization.

Aug 2002 - Apr 2005 **System Administrator** Alsifcom Intermed - Cluj-Napoca, Cluj System administrator in charge with network administration, novell server and windows client stations.

EDUCATION

2002

Engineering Degree: Management of production systems

Technical Univerity | Cluj-Napoca

1997

Secondary Education Exam

Computer Science Highschool | Cluj - Napoca

ACCOMPLISHMENTS

- Certified as AWS Solution Architect Associate (SAA-C01) Validation number: HNLEYH7KJBR1QQ5G
- Certified as AWS SysOps Administrator (SOA-C01) Validation number: RQ55CLE1M21E1X3X

- Improved security by implementing a bastion host with web browser support and 2FA. Serves as single point of entry and connection manager for the team.
- Maintenance plan automation using AWS System Manager
- directory as a service implementation using JumpCloud
- multiple Sitecore 8, 9 XP deployments
- server virtualization using VMware;
- desktop virtualization for the whole group using thin clients;
- migration and consolidation of all virtual desktops in DE datacenter;
- design station virtualization;
- OTRS as ticketing system for the whole group;
- CN datacenter install and configure;
- ERP implementation in RO;
- active directory migration from one forest to a new one.
- Attending classroom trainings: Configuring and Troubleshooting a Windows Server 2008 network Infrastructure; Configuring and troubleshooting Windows Server 2008 Active Directory; Configuring, managing and Maintaining Windows Server 2008; vmWARE vSphere: Troubleshooting; vmWAREvSphere 4.1: Install, Configure, Manage; vmWare vsphere 5.5: Optimize and scale